This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
Now this sight!
Can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cover path across the Grand Line to the New World.
After the Navy's victory in the loss of both Ace and Whitebeard,
the war at Marineford has finally ended.
But this is a story from another time,
ten years ago in the East Blue,
when Luffy first met Ace.
I won't do it!
We're finished here, Brad.
Whoa!
Let him go!
I won't run! Ace's desperate rescue operation!
Forge-a-me! It's that damn kid!
He's got the money! That brat!
Ah!
Huh?
Ace! You're here!
Thanks for showing up, kid. You saved us some trouble.
Your friend ain't squealing. He's pretty tough.
But I think you'll talk.
Ace!
Sa...
Sabo!
Do it!
Boss, are you okay?
Ace!
Sabo!
That kind of hurt.
Who hit me?
You?
You punks don't get who you're messing with.
Yeah.
You're all dead mean!
Shut your mouth and fight!
Sabo! Help Luffy!
You guys!
One thing, that ugly dude has a sword. Be careful!
No way!
Orange of me, that other kid got our knife!
Quick, make a run for it!
You go ahead.
What?
Ace!
Let's just leave!
I don't run from my enemies. Ever!
Got it?
And I don't go easy on my enemies!
Come on!
These guys aren't just thugs! They're Blue Jam Pirates!
Yeah, you got that right.
Now, I'm done playing games here.
You've got something that belongs to us.
Be good, and give it back, you brat!
You're just a kid, and I don't blame you for acting stupid.
But fork over the cash or you'll regret it.
We've got better plans for it. That's our money now.
Then you are dead!
Hold on a sec, I'll be right back.
Oh great, not this again.
Really like to dig your heels in, don't ya?
Shut up. Let's fight.
That's enough of this crap!
I'm not gonna lose, ya hear?
I'd rather just kill myself!
Not if we do it first!
Come at me, you pricks!
I heard the whole damn story, Porchemy.
You should be ashamed.
Did you seriously get beaten by a couple of kids?
Yeah. Forgive me, Captain.
The money.
I've heard enough of this.
You're not fit for my crew.
Now then, which one of you will get my money back?
We gotta show those punks we're not letting it go without a fight, got it?
Yes, Captain.
We'll have it back right away.
Ace, that was really not cool.
Those guys were actual pirates.
Next time, we run.
Whatever your deal is, it's not worth dying over.
This sucks.
I like my old one better.
We made a huge mistake.
Pissing off pirates like that.
Man, they probably told their captain.
What are we supposed to do now?
That was scary!
I thought I was gonna die!
Would you shut up?
You're not hurt that bad.
So stop crying already!
When are you gonna stop being a baby?
Don't you wanna be a pirate?
Thank you.
You...
You saved me.
Stop it!
Calm down.
He's just happy, okay?
All right.
What gives?
Why didn't you tell them what they wanted?
You think they wouldn't kill you cause you're a kid?
Those guys don't give a damn!
I was afraid...
that...
you wouldn't be my friend.
Yeah?
Well, so what?
That still beats dying, right?
Besides, why do you wanna be my friend?
That's dumb.
Because...
It's not like I've been nice to you.
In fact, I've been giving you hell ever since we met.
It's been months.
Why haven't you just given up?
I've just given up.
Well...
Cuz...
Cuz I...
I got no one else to turn to.
I can't go back to Windmill Village.
I don't like the Mountain Bandits either.
I'd be all alone all the time if I didn't follow you.
Getting beat up hurts,
but being lonely hurts more.
Alone?
Why?
Gramps is all I have.
You feel better around me?
Uh-huh.
Otherwise, you feel lonely?
Do I think Gold Roger had a kid?
If he did, then too bad for that poor runt.
No kidding!
They'd put him to death!
He'd probably deserve it, too.
I bet.
Do you think...
I deserve to live?
Of course I do!
I see.
But you're still annoying.
Weak little crybabies piss me off.
I'm not weak!
I'm really strong!
Ha!
You think you're really strong?
You were crying your eyes out the whole time you were tied up.
Have you ever gotten hit by a spiky thing that big?
I'm just seven years old!
Wait till I turn ten years old like you guys,
and then I'll be stronger and won't cry anymore!
Age has nothing to do with it, you brat!
Hell, when I was seven, I was tough!
So what?
I'm gonna be so tough, you're gonna cry!
I promised Shanks I'd be a great pirate someday,
and that means way greater than you!
Ha! You'll be a crappy pirate!
Nuh-uh!
Yeah, huh?
Well, okay, enough of that.
Geez!
Now listen, in case you guys forgot, we got a problem here.
A problem?
Blue Jam and his buddies are bound to come looking for us after what happened back there.
And like you said, they don't care if we're kids, they'll kill us without a second thought.
Yeah, probably.
This forest where I've been living is awfully close to their hideout, the Cove of Pirates.
What if one night I'm a little too tired, sleep a little too hard, and they sneak up on me?
You're dead.
Yeah, way dead.
Right.
So, I need your help.
Here, I've got an idea.
What's with all the bandages? Have they been fighting bears or something?
That's not the problem.
Hey! Boss! Come quick! This isn't good!
Give me a sec, it's early.
Huh?
What have those breasts been up to now?
One, two...
Huh?
Ace, Luffy.
Wait a sec.
Huh?
Ace, Luffy.
Okay.
Okay, let's work this out.
Ace, Luffy.
Huh?
Ace, Luffy!
Who's that other kid with you?
Who's what now?
Come on.
It's too early for questions.
Pipe down, will ya?
Two brats is already too many!
Who the hell are you?
You mean me?
Ugh!
Right.
Hi, I'm Sabo.
Huh?
Ace's friend, I see.
Oh good.
It's like I'm already living here.
And you must be Dadan, right?
Hiya!
Living here?
Listen up, kid.
Nobody said you could stay.
Don't answer me with a fart!
Hey, quit farting in my house!
You're just as worthless as those other two low-lifes moving off me!
Oh yeah?
Well I heard that you're a worthless old hag yourself.
Uh-uh!
Pull that crap one more time and you're out of here!
Actually, you're out anyway.
I ain't watching any more brats.
I also heard that you're a nice old hag that wouldn't leave a kid like me to die in the woods.
Huh?
And you're a tough old hag too, so I'll be sure to mind my manners.
Okay, the tough part is true, but stop calling me a hag!
You stupid brats!
Luffy!
Ace!
Sabo!
There aren't any free rides!
You twerps better be grateful and get to work this instant!
You got it!
Thank you!
See ya!
Hey!
Get back here, Luffy!
This house ain't gonna clean itself!
Cleaning is boring!
Bleh!
Hey, Sabo!
Wait for me!
Damn brats!
I should've known!
Oops!
Hold it!
Forgot to tell them!
Hey, Dad!
You might get some gas later!
We pissed off Blue Jam so he probably wants us dead!
Play it cool, okay?
Hold on!
Is this supposed to be a joke?
I'm lost!
Huh?
It's true!
We beat his crew up!
And that's why I had to move you!
Hey!
See ya!
Later!
Waaaah!
Dada'n's cool!
I really like how she just lets us do whatever we want!
Meh, she's still a worthless ol' hag.
Yeah, she's real ugly!
Like a butt!
Anyway, now what?
Well, first off...
Let's eat!
Ha ha!
Okay, time to eat!
Got to keep our strength up.
Hey, Luffy.
I heard you ate a devil fruit.
Is that true?
Yep.
I see.
So that means you can't swim, huh?
Here.
You can have a tail.
Thanks, Sabo.
You're too nice.
Yeah?
What's wrong with that?
So, which fruit did you eat?
Gum-gum fruit.
Gum-gum?
What's that?
Like rubber.
Who wants to be made of rubber?
And you can't even swim?
That's so lame.
It's totally awesome!
Because I got all these cool special moves that only I can do.
Fine.
You win.
But if your special moves are so cool, why don't you make one that'll catch us some fish, you freeloader?
His whole body really is made of rubber.
That's neat!
Let go of my face!
You know, if you got into a fight, stretching, or bouncing, it might actually be kind of handy.
Uh-huh!
It is!
And I just made up my best move yet!
I call this one the gum-gum balloon!
It can bounce back cannonballs and bullets and lots of stuff!
Whoa!
Can you show me right now?
Sure!
I'll do it just for you!
That meanie doesn't get to see it!
Don't peek!
Here we go!
Gum-gum!
Dude!
That's nuts!
You keep getting bigger!
You're not going to pop, are you?
Oh-oh!
Everything bounces right off!
Well, not sure I'd use the word cool.
And you bounce right off my foot!
Sabo!
Kick him back here!
Oh-uh-huh?
Gum-gum balloon!
You're right, Luffy!
Your gum-gum moves are pretty neat!
Gum-gum!
Hey!
If you can block cannonballs, then try blocking this!
Gum-gum balloon!
Ah!
Whoa!
Wait, you can't just eat a guy then run away like that!
Astam out!
Ah!
Gu-guys!
Ha-ha!
Yeah, sometimes that happens, right?
No, it doesn't!
I almost got eaten back there!
Don't try to play it off!
Get over it.
We got lots of crocodile meat for dinner, so it worked out.
Mmm, good point!
Uh, that was fast.
But I want to have some crocodile right now!
I can't wait till dinner!
Ace!
Hmm?
Uh, before we get back to the hag's place, I want to check something.
Can you come with me?
See anything in there?
Look carefully!
Man, it's a good thing we moved our pirate savings.
Yeah.
While we're at it, you want to check Grey Terminal, too?
Good idea.
Ace, Luffy, you two head back.
I'll catch up.
Ah!
He won't listen to anyone.
Good grief!
This place is swarming with the usual punks and Blue Jams guys.
And they mean business.
Well, what did you expect?
Blue Jams got to be super pissed right now.
Huh?
Hey, guys!
Those kids you've been looking for are right here!
All three of them!
What?
He's right!
Grab them!
Give it up!
There's a bounty on your head and I've got to catch it in!
Huh.
Well, that just sucks.
Blue Jams got all of Grey Terminal hunting us down.
We'd better lay low for now.
There's too many of them.
Here's hoping they get bored and move on to something else.
Why should we hide?
If they find us, then we can just fight them.
That's no reason to pick a fight, though.
What?
Are we going to beat up like a hundred guys just because?
Yay!
Stubble's right!
Nobody asked you.
Blue Jams?
The kids sure know how to screw us over.
I'm sure those pirates are going to find out about this place pretty soon.
Oh, man.
We're going to be in big trouble.
We're tough, but no way we can beat Blue Jams, man.
Maybe this is the end of the Dadan family.
We've had a great run, guys.
But it's time to say goodbye to the Mountain Bandit's life.
All of our crimes are coming back to bite us in the ass.
Live by the sword.
Die by the sword.
We should have known.
Had a great run?
We can't beat them?
How pathetic can you numbskulls get?
Don't you take any pride in being Mountain Bandits all these years?
This is simple.
If they come by asking for the brats,
we'll just hand Ace and Luffy and that stupid new kid right on over.
Yeah, but boss, there's Garp.
He'll get angry at us if we do that.
Plus, that Blue Jam guy's a monster.
If he finds out we even know those kids,
he'll kill us just for the hell of it.
Well, then...
Yes?
Then we'll play dumb.
Yeah, just pretend we don't know them.
Now, let's try it.
Be real dumb.
Hey, guys.
Have you seen Ace and Sawbo?
They stay in here?
Spit it out or else.
We don't know.
That was bad.
Boss!
Ace and those other brats are back.
Huh?
Fearing for his life,
Sabo left Grey Terminal and found a home with Ace and Luffy,
much to Dedan's dismay.
For the three unwanted guests, it was a never-ending party.
Making any excuse to get out of their daily chores,
they hunted wild animals in the mountains,
tussled with hooligans in the city,
and dueled with pirates of the cove.
Within time, news of their wild exploits reached far and wide,
even over the high walls surrounding the center of the kingdom.
Luffy, Ace, and Sawbo make a name for themselves in Grey Terminal.
While celebrating their latest victory,
a surprising truth about Sawbo is revealed,
and the boys make a promise to one another
that will shape their future.
On the next, One Piece, to the sea someday!
The Pledge of the Three Brats!
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!